Don't trust and rely too much on your followers
Не слишком доверяйся своим приближённым
Don't become their puppet
не становись их марионеткой
You and your elder brother are family
ты и твой старший брат  одна семья
This realm
Это царство
Will always belong to the Sikong family
всегда принадлежало роду Сыкун
Your son understands
Сын всё понял
Go
Иди
Your son
Ваш сын
Takes leave
Ваш сын откланивается
Prince of Jin
Принц Цзинь
Miss Chen
Госпожа Чэнь
What a coincidence
Какая удача
I'm here on my granduncle's orders
по поручению дяди
To report to His Majesty
как раз иду доложить важное Его Величеству
I've discovered
Я выяснила
The trouble in Qing Province
что смута в Цинчжоу
Was someone deliberately framing Prince of Ning
дело рук тех кто хотел подставить князя Нина
Could it be Miss Chen
Неужто госпожа Чэнь
Has already found the mastermind?
уже нашла зачинщика
That's right
Верно
Drag him over for Prince of Jin to see
Приведите  пусть Его Высочество взглянет
His name is Guo Xuan
Его зовут Го Сюань
Son of the Governor of Qing Province
он сын цинчжоуского правителя
The canal project was obstructed
Нарушения в строительстве канала
And sparked rebellion
и народное волнение
Precisely because this man and his father
всё это устроено им и его отцом
Were manipulating behind the scenes
за кулисами
The Chancellor
Премьерминистр
Will submit a memorial tomorrow to impeach
Завтра премьерминистр направит доклад с требованием расследовать преступления семьи Го
And thoroughly investigate the Guo family's crimes
расследовать преступления рода Го
A provincial governor
Целого губернатора
Just to take the blame
использовать для искупления вины
The Chen family, to get elder brother out
Род Чэнь чтобы освободить старшего брата
Has really gone all out
пошёл вабанк
How should I respond?
Что же мне им ответить